[
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "Banks in the early 19th century in the U.S. were created to handle increasing amounts of savings and prevent fraud.",
      "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "Peer-to-peer lending requires the intervention of traditional banks.",
      "Answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "Low interest rates in the 2000s led to a housing bubble.",
      "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Warren Buffett’s investment strategy is known for being high-risk.",
      "Answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "The Federal Reserve adjusts interest rates to discourage borrowing during economic downturns.",
      "Answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "China controls its credit markets to direct lending towards specific sectors.",
      "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "Prolonged low interest rates encourage long-term economic stability.",
      "Answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "Max Goodbank’s cautious approach avoided risky ventures and ensured stability.",
      "Answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "The subprime mortgage crisis was caused by careful lending practices.",
      "Answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "Peer-to-peer lending platforms are part of the traditional banking system.",
      "Answer": "False"
    }
  ]
  